<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kubrick.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Кубрик</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Kubrik</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Кубрик</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Kubrik</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKubrickxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kubrick</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Kubrick</name>
  <summary>3-D Game based on Rubik's Cube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc en 3D basat en el cub de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc en 3D basat en el cub de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">3D hra založená na Rubikově kostce</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">3D-spil baseret på Rubiks terning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">3D-Spiel wie „Rubiks Würfel“</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Τρισδιάστατο παιχνίδι με βάση τον κύβο του Ρούμπικ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">3-D Game based on Rubik's Cube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">3-D-ludo bazita sur Rubik-Kubo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego 3D basado en el cubo de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">3-D mäng, mille eeskujuks on Rubiku kuubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Rubik-en kuboan oinarritutako 3-D jokoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Rubikin kuutioon perustuva kolmiulotteinen peli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu 3D inspiré du Rubik's Cube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xogo en tres dimensións baseado no cubo de Rubik.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">A Rubik kockán alapuló 3D-s játék</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Joco de 3-D basate sur le Cubo de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan 3-D berdasarkan pada Rubik's Cube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco 3-D basato sul cubo di Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">3D თამაში, ბაზირებული რუბიკის კუბზე</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">루빅스 큐브 기반 3D 게임</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">3D-spel gebaseerd op de Rubik's kubus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">3D-spel basert på Rubiks kube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra 3-D oparta na kostce Rubika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo 3-D baseado no Cubo de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um jogo 3-D baseado no Cubo Mágico de Rubik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Трёхмерная игра, основанная на кубике Рубика</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">3D hra založená na Rubikovej kocke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">3-D igra Rubikove kocke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">3Д игра на основу Рубикове коцке</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">3D igra na osnovu Rubikove kocke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">3Д игра на основу Рубикове коцке</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">3D igra na osnovu Rubikove kocke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Tredimensionellt spel baserat på Rubiks kub</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">3B Rubik Küpü Temelli Oyun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Просторова гра, заснована на кубику Рубіка</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xx3-D Game based on Rubik's Cubexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">三维魔方游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">立體的魔術方塊遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kubrick is a game based on the Rubik's Cube™ puzzle. The cube sizes range
      from 2x2x2 up to 6x6x6, or you can play with irregular "bricks" such as 5x3x2
      or "mats" such as 6x4x1 or 2x2x1. The game has a selection of puzzles at
      several levels of difficulty, as well as demos of pretty patterns and
      solution moves, or you can make up your own puzzles.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kubrick és un joc basat en el puzle del Cub de Rubik™. L'interval de mides del cub és des de 2x2x2 a 6x6x6, o es pot jugar amb «maons» irregulars com 5x3x2 o «mats» com 6x4x1 o 2x2x1. El joc té una selecció de trencaclosques de diversos nivells de dificultat, així com demostracions amb patrons interessants i moviments de solució, o es poden construir trencaclosques propis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kubrick és un joc basat en el puzle del Cub de Rubik™. L'interval de mides del cub és des de 2x2x2 a 6x6x6, o es pot jugar amb «maons» irregulars com 5x3x2 o «mats» com 6x4x1 o 2x2x1. El joc té una selecció de trencaclosques de diversos nivells de dificultat, així com demostracions amb patrons interessants i moviments de solució, o es poden construir trencaclosques propis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Kubrick er et spil baseret på Rubik's Cube™-gådelegetøjet. Terningens størrelse varierer fra 2x2x2 op til 6x6x6, eller du kan lege med uregelmæssige "terninger" såsom 5x3x2 eller "måtter" såsom 6x4x1 eller 2x2x1. Spillet har et udvalg af gådespil  med forskellige sværhedsgrader, såvel som demoer af flotte mønstre  og løsningstræk, eller du kan opfinde dine egne gådespil.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kubrick basiert auf Rubiks Würfel™. Es sind Würfel mit einer Kantenlänge von 2×2×2 bis 6×6×6, Quader (z. B. 5×3×2) oder Matten (z. B. 6×4×1 oder 2×2×1) wählbar. Das Spiel bietet eine Auswahl verschieden-verdrehter Würfel bei unterschiedlichen Schwierigkeitsgraden und Demos von schönen Würfel und Lösungsversuche. Es können auch eigene Würfel erstellt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Kubrick είναι ένα παιχνίδι με βάση το γρίφο Rubik's Cube™. Το εύρος μεγεθών του κύβου είναι από 2x2x2 έως 6x6x6 ή μπορείτε ακόμη να πάιξετε και με ακανόνιστα «τούβλα» όπως 5x3x2 ή «πατάκια» 6x4x1 ή 2x2x1. Το παιχνίδι έχει μια επιλογή γρίφων σε διάφορα επίπεδα δυσκολίας, καθώς επίσης και παρουσιάσεις όμορφων μοτίβων και κινήσεων επίλυσης, ή να σχεδιάσετε το δικό σας γρίφο.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kubrick is a game based on the Rubik's Cube™ puzzle. The cube sizes range from 2x2x2 up to 6x6x6, or you can play with irregular "bricks" such as 5x3x2 or "mats" such as 6x4x1 or 2x2x1. The game has a selection of puzzles at several levels of difficulty, as well as demos of pretty patterns and solution moves, or you can make up your own puzzles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Kubrick estas ludo bazita sur la enigmo de Rubik's Cube™. La grandecoj de la kubo varias de 2x2x2 ĝis 6x6x6, aŭ vi povas ludi per neregulaj "brikoj" kiel 5x3x2 aŭ "matoj" kiel 6x4x1 aŭ 2x2x1. La ludo havas elekton de enigmoj je pluraj niveloj de malfacileco, kaj ankaŭ demonstraĵojn de belaj ŝablonoj kaj solvomovoj, aŭ vi povas elpensi viajn proprajn enigmojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kubrick es un juego basado en el rompecabezas del Cubo de Rubik™. El tamaño del cubo puede variar entre 2x2x2 y 6x6x6, aunque también puede jugar con «ladrillos» irregulares (como 5x3x2) o de tipo «alfombra» (como 6x4x1 o 2x2x1). El juego contiene una selección de rompecabezas de varios niveles de dificultad, así como demostraciones de diseños interesantes y movimientos de solución. También puede crear sus propios rompecabezas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kubrick põhineb kogu maailmas tuntud Rubiku kuubikul. Kuubiku suurus võib olla vahemikus 2x2x2 kui 6x6x6, mängida võib ebakorrapäraste "tahukatega", näiteks 5x3x2, või ka "tasapindadega", näiteks 6x4x1 või 2x2x1. Mängus saab valida mitme raskusastme vahel, samuti saab demode abil uurida kauneid mustreid ja lahenduskäike, soovi korral võib aga kuubiku päris ise koostada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kubrick, Rubik's Cube™ buru-hausgarrian oinarritutako joko bat da. Kuboaren neurria 2x2x2 eta 6x6x6 artekoa da, edo "adreilu" irregularrekin josta zaitezke, 5x3x2 esaterako, edo "tapizekin" 6x4x1 edo 2x2x1. Jokoak hainbat zailtasun mailako buru-hausgarrien hautapen bat dauka, baita eredu ederren erakusgarriak eta ebazpen mugimenduak. Zeure buru-hausgarria ere sor dezakezu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kubrick on Rubikin kuutioon perustuva peli. Kuution koko vaihtelee 2 × 2 × 2:sta 6 × 6 × 6:een. Voit myös pelata epäsäännöllisin 5 × 3 × 2 ”lohkoin” tai 6 × 4 × 1 tai 2 × 2 × 1 ”matoin”. Pelissä on valikoima vaikeudeltaan eritasoisia tehtäviä samoin kuin demoja asetelmista tai ratkaisusiirroista. Voit myös luoda omia tehtäviäsi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kubrick est un jeu inspiré du casse-tête Rubik's Cube™. Les tailles des cubes vont de 2x2x2 à 6x6x6, vous pouvez également jouer avec des « prismes », par exemple de 5x3x2, 6x4x1 ou 2x2x1. Le jeu propose une sélection de casse-têtes de différentes difficultés, ainsi que des démonstrations des solutions et d'autres motifs originaux, vous pouvez également construire vos propres casse-têtes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Kubrick é un xogo baseado no Cubo de Rubik™. Os tamaños do cubo van desde 2x2x2 ata 6x6x6 e tamén se pode xogar con «ladrillos» irregulares como 5x3x2 ou «felpudos» de 6x4x1 ou de 2x2x1. O xogo goza dunha escolla de quebracabezas con varios niveis de dificultade, así como demostracións de padróns bonitos e movementos de solución - e tamén podes crear os teus propios quebracabezas…</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Kubrick egy, a Rubik-kockán™ alapuló kirakós játék. A kocka méretei a 2x2x2-től a 6x6x6-ig terjednek, de játszhat szabálytalan „téglákkal” is, például 5x3x2-esekkel, vagy „szőnyegekkel”, például 6x4x1-es vagy 2x2x1-es méretűekkel. A játékban többféle nehézségi fokozatú rejtvények, valamint szép minták és megoldási lépések demói találhatók, de saját rejtvényeket is kitalálhat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Kubrick adalah permainan berdasarkan pada permainan teka-teki Rubik's Cube™. Jarak ukuran kubus dari 2x2x2 sampai 6x6x6, atau kamu bisa memainkan dengan sembarang "bricks" seperti 5x3x2 atau "mats" seperti 6x4x1 atau 2x2x1. Permainan harus memilih teka-teki di beberapa level sulit, begitu juga demo-demo dari pola-pola yang cantik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kubrick è un gioco basato sul cubo di Rubik™. Le dimensioni del cubo variano da 2x2x2 fino a 6x6x6, oppure si può giocare con «mattonelle» fino a 5x3x2 o «piatti» come 6x4x1 o 2x2x1. Il gioco contiene una selezione di rompicapi a diversi livelli di difficoltà, così come dimostrazioni di mosse interessanti e gradevoli e di soluzioni, oppure puoi costruire dei rompicapi come preferisci.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Kubrick რუბიკის კუბზე™ დაფუძნებული თამაშია. კუბის ზომები 2x2x2-დან 6x6x6-მდე იცვლება ან შეგიძლიათ, უფორმო "აგურებით" ითამაშოთ, მაგ 5x3x2 ან 6x4x1 ან 2x2x1. თამაშს რამდენიმე დონის სირთულის მოზაიკები მოჰყვება ისევე, როგორც დემოები და ამომხსნელი სვლები, ან, მოზაიკა შეგიძლიათ, თვითონაც შექმნათ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Kubrick은 루빅스 큐브 퍼즐 기반 게임입니다. 최소 2x2x2부터 최대 6x6x6까지 정육면체 큐브나, 5x3x2 등 크기의 비정형 "벽돌"이나 6x4x1 또는 2x2x1 크기의 "매트"가 될 수도 있습니다. 게임에는 여러 다양한 난이도가 있으며, 흥미있는 패턴과 풀이법을 표시하는 데모 모드를 지원합니다. 사용자 정의 퍼즐을 만들 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kubrick is een spel gebaseerd op de Rubik's Cube™ puzzel. De afmetingen van de kubus variëren van 2x2x2 tot aan 6x6x6, maar u kunt ook met onregelmatige "stenen" zoals 5x3x2 of "matten" zoals 6x4x1 of 2x2x1 spelen. Het spel heeft een verzameling puzzels met verschillende moeilijkheidsgraden, maar ook demo´s van mooie patronen en oplossingen, maar u kunt ook uw eigen puzzels maken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Kubrick er eit spel basert på Rubiks kube. Kubane kjem i storleik frå 2 × 2 × 2 til 6 × 6 × 6, og du kan òg spela med uvanlege «blokker», som 5 × 3 × 2, eller «matter», som 6 × 4 × 1. Spelet har eit utval utfordringar med ulike vanskegradar. Du kan òg sjå demonstrasjonar av flotte mønster og løysingar, eller laga dine eigne oppgåver.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kubrick jest grą opartą na układance Kostki Rubika™. Rozmiary kostki są w zakresie od 2x2x2 aż do 6x6x6, ale można także grać 'nieforemnymi' kostkami takimi jak 5x3x2 lub "matami" takimi jak 6x4x1 lub 2x2x1. Gra zawiera wybór układanek na kilku poziomach trudności, a także dema ładnych wzorów i ruchów rozwiązujących. Jest także możliwość stworzenia własnej układanki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kubrick é um jogo baseado no 'puzzle' Cubo de Rubik™. Os tamanhos dos cubos variam de 2x2x2 até 6x6x6, ou então poderá lidar com "tijolos" irregulares, como o 5x3x2 ou "tabletes" do tipo 6x4x1 ou 2x2x1. O jogo tem  uma selecção de 'puzzles' com diferentes níveis de dificuldade, assim como demonstração de padrões bonitos e jogadas de solução, podendo você também criar os seus próprios 'puzzles'.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kubrick é um jogo baseado no puzzle do Cubo de Rubik™ ou também conhecido como Cubo Mágico. Os tamanhos dos cubos variam de 2x2x2 até 6x6x6, podendo também jogar com "tijolos" irregulares, como o 5x3x2 ou "tabletes" como o 6x4x1 ou 2x2x1. O jogo tem uma seleção de puzzles com diversos níveis de dificuldade, assim como demonstrações de padrões bonitos e solução de jogadas, podendo também criar os seus próprios puzzles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Kubrick — игра на основе кубика Рубика. Доступны размеры кубика от 2x2x2 до 6x6x6, а также возможно играть с неровными «брусками» (например, 5x3x2) или «плоскостями» (например, 6x4x1 или 2x2x1). В игре представлен набор головоломок для нескольких уровней сложности, а также демонстрации интересных шаблонов и хода решения. Кроме того, поддерживается создание пользовательских головоломок.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kubrick je hra založená na Rubikovej kocke. Veľkosť kocky je v rozsahu od 2x2x2 do 6x6x6 alebo môžete hrať s nepravidelnými tehlami, napríklad 5x3x2 alebo rohožkami 6x4x1 alebo 2x2x1. Hra má výber skladačiek v niekoľkých úrovniach obtiažnosti, ako aj ukážky pekných vzorov a riešení pohybov alebo si môžete vytvoriť vlastné puzzle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kubrick je igra, ki temelji na sestavljanki imenovani Rubikova kocka. Velikosti kocke se razprostirajo od 2x2x2 pa do 6x6x6, igrate pa lahko tudi s sestavljankami, ki niso kocke (npr. 5x3x2, 6x4x1 ali 2x2x1). Igra ima izbor sestavljank več težavnostnih stopenj, kot tudi predstavitvenih načinov z lepimi vzorci in njihovimi rešitvami. Po želji pa lahko ustvarite tudi lastne sestavljanke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Кубрик је игра на основу слагалице „Рубикова коцка“. Величина коцке иде од 2×2×2 до 6×6×6, а можете играти и са неправилним „циглама“, попут 5×3×2, и „плочама“, попут 6×4×1 или 2×2×1. Игра пружа избор слагалица са неколико нивоа тежине, као и демонстрације лепих образаца и потеза за решавање, а можете правити и сопствене слагалице.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Kubrik je igra na osnovu slagalice „Rubikova kocka“. Veličina kocke ide od 2×2×2 do 6×6×6, a možete igrati i sa nepravilnim „ciglama“, poput 5×3×2, i „pločama“, poput 6×4×1 ili 2×2×1. Igra pruža izbor slagalica sa nekoliko nivoa težine, kao i demonstracije lepih obrazaca i poteza za rešavanje, a možete praviti i sopstvene slagalice.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Кубрик је игра на основу слагалице „Рубикова коцка“. Величина коцке иде од 2×2×2 до 6×6×6, а можете играти и са неправилним „циглама“, попут 5×3×2, и „плочама“, попут 6×4×1 или 2×2×1. Игра пружа избор слагалица са неколико нивоа тежине, као и демонстрације лепих образаца и потеза за решавање, а можете правити и сопствене слагалице.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Kubrik je igra na osnovu slagalice „Rubikova kocka“. Veličina kocke ide od 2×2×2 do 6×6×6, a možete igrati i sa nepravilnim „ciglama“, poput 5×3×2, i „pločama“, poput 6×4×1 ili 2×2×1. Igra pruža izbor slagalica sa nekoliko nivoa težine, kao i demonstracije lepih obrazaca i poteza za rešavanje, a možete praviti i sopstvene slagalice.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kubrick är ett spel baserat på Rubiks Kub™. Kubstorlekarna går från 2 x 2 x 2 upp till 6 x 6 x 6, eller så kan man spela med oregelbundna "tegelstenar" såsom 5 x 3 x 2, eller "mattor" såsom 6 x 4 x 1 eller 2 x 2 x 1. Programmet innehåller ett urval av spel med flera svårighetsnivåer, samt demonstrationer av vackra mönster och lösningar, eller så kan man skapa egna spel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kubrick, Rubik's Cube™ bulmacasına dayanan bir oyundur. Küp boyutları 2x2x2 ila 6x6x6 arasında değişebilir veya 5x3x2 gibi düzensiz "tuğlalar" veya 6x4x1 veya 2x2x1 gibi "paspaslar" ile oynayabilirsiniz. Oyunun çeşitli zorluk düzeylerde bulmacalar yanısıra, güzel desen ve çözüm hamleli demolar oynayabilir veya kendi bulmacanızı yapabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kubrick — це гра, яку засновано на головоломці Кубик Рубіка™. Розміри кубика можуть змінюватися у межах від 2x2x2 до 6x6x6, крім того, ви можете грати з неправильними «цеглинками», з розмірами на зразок 5x3x2, або «килимками», з розмірами на зразок 6x4x1 або 2x2x1. У цій грі ви можете обирати головоломки декількох рівнів складності, спостерігати за демонстрацією чудових візерунків та обертань розв’язання та створювати власні головоломки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKubrick is a game based on the Rubik's Cube™ puzzle. The cube sizes range from 2x2x2 up to 6x6x6, or you can play with irregular "bricks" such as 5x3x2 or "mats" such as 6x4x1 or 2x2x1. The game has a selection of puzzles at several levels of difficulty, as well as demos of pretty patterns and solution moves, or you can make up your own puzzles.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kubrick</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kubrick</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kubrick</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kubrick&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Kubrick in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">El Kubrick en acció</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kubrick en acció</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Kubrick i brug</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Kubrick in Aktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Το Kubrick σε δράση</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Kubrick in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Kubrick en aktivo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Kubrick en acción</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Mängimine Kubrickuga</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kubrick martxan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kubrick toiminnassa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Kubrick en action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Kubrick en acción.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A Kubrick játék közben</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Kubrick in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Kubrick beraksi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Kubrick in azione</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Kubrick მუშაობისას</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Kubrick 플레이</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Kubrick in actie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Kubrick i praksis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Kubrick w działaniu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O Kubrick em acção</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Kubrick em ação</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Kubrick в действии</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Kubrick v akcií</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Kubrick v akciji</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Kubrick i aktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kubrick çalışırken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Kubrick під час гри</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKubrick in actionxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">動作中的 Kubrick</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kubrick.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kubrick.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>kubrick</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.1.24021" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="1.1.24020" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="1.1.23085" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="1.1.23084" date="2023-12-07"/>
  </releases>
</component>
